[
  [
    {
      "heading": "Cultural Preferences",
      "questions": [
        {
          "answer": " API result: { success: true, response: '{}' }",
          "type": "checkbox",
          "code": null,
          "question": "Respond to each option below.",
          "id": 3000,
          "options": [
            {
              "id": 2002,
              "label": "Spiritual or cultural practice that impacts healthcare"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "heading": "Patient Living Situation",
      "questions": [
        {
          "answer": "{ qn_id: 3001, option_ids: [ 2027 ], t_id: [ 'SSL1', 'SSL2' ] }",
          "type": "radio",
          "code": "(M1100)",
          "question": "Which of the following best describes the patient's residential circumstance and availability of assistance? (Check one box only.)",
          "id": 3001,
          "options": [
            {
              "id": 2018,
              "label": "a. Patient lives alone (Living Arrangement)"
            },
            {
              "id": 2019,
              "label": "a. Patient lives alone (Around the Clock)"
            },
            {
              "id": 2020,
              "label": "a. Patient lives alone (Regular Daytime)"
            },
            {
              "id": 2021,
              "label": "a. Patient lives alone (Regular Nighttime)"
            },
            {
              "id": 2022,
              "label": "a. Patient lives alone (Occasional/ Short-Term Assistance)"
            },
            {
              "id": 2023,
              "label": "b. Patient lives with other person(s) in the home (Living Arrangement)"
            },
            {
              "id": 2024,
              "label": "b. Patient lives with other person(s) in the home (Around the Clock)"
            },
            {
              "id": 2025,
              "label": "b. Patient lives with other person(s) in the home (Regular Daytime)"
            },
            {
              "id": 2026,
              "label": "b. Patient lives with other person(s) in the home (Regular Nighttime)"
            },
            {
              "id": 2027,
              "label": "b. Patient lives with other person(s) in the home (Occasional/ Short-Term Assistance)"
            },
            {
              "id": 2028,
              "label": "c. Patient lives in congregate situation (e.g., assisted living, residential care home) (Living Arrangement)"
            },
            {
              "id": 2029,
              "label": "c. Patient lives in congregate situation (e.g., assisted living, residential care home) (Around the Clock)"
            },
            {
              "id": 2030,
              "label": "c. Patient lives in congregate situation (e.g., assisted living, residential care home) (Regular Daytime)"
            },
            {
              "id": 2031,
              "label": "c. Patient lives in congregate situation (e.g., assisted living, residential care home) (Regular Nighttime)"
            },
            {
              "id": 2032,
              "label": "c. Patient lives in congregate situation (e.g., assisted living, residential care home) (Occasional/ Short-Term Assistance)"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "heading": "Transportation",
      "questions": [
        {
          "answer":" [ { qn_id: 3003, option_ids: [ 2040 ], t_id: [ 'SSL3' ] } ]",
          "type": "checkbox",
          "code": "(A1250)",
          "question": "Transportation (NACHC ©)",
          "id": 3003,
          "options": [
            {
              "id": 2038,
              "label": "A. Yes, it has kept me from medical appointments or from getting my medications"
            },
            {
              "id": 2039,
              "label": "B. Yes, it has kept me from non-medical meetings, appointments, work or from getting things that I need"
            },
            {
              "id": 2040,
              "label": "C. No"
            },
            {
              "id": 2041,
              "label": "X.  Patient unable to respond"
            },
            {
              "id": 2042,
              "label": "Y. Patient declines to respond"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "heading": "Health Literacy",
      "questions": [
        {
          "answer":"{ qn_id: 3004, option_ids: [ 2054 ], t_id: [ 'SSL4' ] }",
          "type": "radio",
          "code": "(B1300)",
          "question": "Health Literacy (from Creative Commons ©)",
          "id": 3004,
          "options": [
            {
              "label": "0. Never",
              "id": 2050
            },
            {
              "label": "1. Rarely",
              "id": 2051
            },
            {
              "label": "2. Sometimes",
              "id": 2052
            },
            {
              "label": "3. Often",
              "id": 2053
            },
            {
              "label": "4. Always",
              "id": 2054
            },
            {
              "label": "7. Patient declines to respond",
              "id": 2055
            },
            {
              "label": "8. Patient unable to respond",
              "id": 2056
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "heading": "Plan of Care: Psychosocial Assessment",
      "questions": [
        {
          "answer": {
            "3005": {
              "option_ids": [
                2064
              ],
              "t_id": [
                "SSL5"
              ],
              "comments": "Home environment safety concerns: narrow passages and long winding staircase"
            }
          },
          "type": "checkbox",
          "code": null,
          "question": "Select all that apply. Selections will populate in the Plan of Care.",
          "id": 3005,
          "options": [
            {
              "id": 2063,
              "label": "No problems identified"
            },
            {
              "id": 2064,
              "label": "Home environment, altered:"
            },
            {
              "id": 2065,
              "label": "Suspected abuse/neglect:"
            },
            {
              "id": 2066,
              "label": "Barriers to health status:"
            },
            {
              "id": 2067,
              "label": "Community resources needed:"
            },
            {
              "id": 2068,
              "label": "Community resources providing assistance:"
            }
          ],
          "comments": {
            "question": "Comments:",
            "placeholder": ""
          }
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "heading": "Plan of Care: Caregiver Status",
      "questions": [
        {
          "answer": {
            "answer": {
              "3007": {
                "value": "Primary caregiver is the daughter and provides occasional assistance, primarily driving to appointments; no extensive assistance required.",
                "t_id": [
                  "SSL2"
                ]
              }
            }
          },
          "type": "textarea",
          "code": null,
          "question": "Caregiver Availability/Type of Assistance",
          "id": 3007,
          "placeholder": "Enter Caregiver Availability/Type of Assistance"
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "heading": "Plan of Care: Safety Measures",
      "questions": [
        {
          "answer": {
            "qn_id": 3008,
            "option_ids": [
              2097,
              2100,
              2101,
              2102,
              2110,
              2116,
              2117
            ],
            "t_id": [
              "C4",
              "M8",
              "SSL5",
              "F3",
              "F4",
              "F5",
              "F6",
              "F7"
            ]
          },
          "type": "checkbox",
          "code": null,
          "question": "Select all that apply. Selections will populate in the Plan of Care.",
          "id": 3008,
          "options": [
            {
              "id": 2094,
              "label": "24-hour supervision"
            },
            {
              "id": 2095,
              "label": "Aspiration precautions"
            },
            {
              "id": 2096,
              "label": "Bleeding precautions"
            },
            {
              "id": 2097,
              "label": "Diabetic: Do not cut nails."
            },
            {
              "id": 2098,
              "label": "DME and electrical safety"
            },
            {
              "id": 2099,
              "label": "Elevate head of bed"
            },
            {
              "id": 2100,
              "label": "Emergency/disaster plan development"
            },
            {
              "id": 2101,
              "label": "Fall precautions"
            },
            {
              "id": 2102,
              "label": "Keep pathways clear"
            },
            {
              "id": 2103,
              "label": "Neutropenic precautions"
            },
            {
              "id": 2104,
              "label": "O2 precautions"
            },
            {
              "id": 2105,
              "label": "Presence of animals:"
            },
            {
              "id": 2106,
              "label": "Prone to skin breakdown precaution"
            },
            {
              "id": 2107,
              "label": "Prone to fractures precaution"
            },
            {
              "id": 2108,
              "label": "Proper positioning during meals"
            },
            {
              "id": 2109,
              "label": "Proper handling of biohazard waste"
            },
            {
              "id": 2110,
              "label": "Safety in ADLs"
            },
            {
              "id": 2111,
              "label": "Seizure precautions"
            },
            {
              "id": 2112,
              "label": "Sharps safety"
            },
            {
              "id": 2113,
              "label": "Side rails up"
            },
            {
              "id": 2114,
              "label": "Slow position changes"
            },
            {
              "id": 2115,
              "label": "Infection control:"
            },
            {
              "id": 2116,
              "label": "Support during transfer and ambulation"
            },
            {
              "id": 2117,
              "label": "Use of assistive devices"
            },
            {
              "id": 2118,
              "label": "Other:"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
,
    {
      "heading": "Plan of Care: Vital Sign Parameters",
      "questions": [
        {
          "answer": {
            "qn_id": 3017,
            "value": 72,
            "option_ids": [],
            "t_id": [
              "C3"
            ]
          },
          "type": "number",
          "code": null,
          "question": "Pulse Rate (bpm): greater than (>)",
          "id": 3017,
          "placeholder": "Enter Number"
        },
        {
          "answer": "{ '3020': { value: 72, option_ids: [], t_id: [ 'C3' ] } }",
          "type": "number",
          "code": null,
          "question": "Pulse Rate (bpm): or less than (<)",
          "id": 3020,
          "placeholder": "Enter Number"
        },
        {
          "type": "number",
          "code": null,
          "question": "Temperature (°F): greater than (>)",
          "id": 3022,
          "placeholder": "Enter Number"
        },
        {
          "type": "number",
          "code": null,
          "question": "Temperature (°F): or less than (<)",
          "id": 3025,
          "placeholder": "Enter Number"
        },
        {
          "answer": {
            "3027": {
              "value": 77,
              "option_ids": [],
              "t_id": [
                "C3"
              ]
            }
          },
          "type": "number",
          "code": null,
          "question": "Respirations (/min): greater than (>)",
          "id": 3027,
          "placeholder": "Enter Number"
        },
        {
          "answer": "{ '3030': { value: '77', option_ids: [], t_id: [ 'C3' ] } }",
          "type": "number",
          "code": null,
          "question": "Respirations (/min): or less than (<)",
          "id": 3030,
          "placeholder": "Enter Number"
        },
        {
          "type": "number",
          "code": null,
          "question": "O2 Saturation (%): less than (<)",
          "id": 3032,
          "placeholder": "Enter Number"
        },
        {
          "answer": " { '3035': 4, t_id: [ 'P3' ] }",
          "type": "number",
          "code": null,
          "question": "Pain Level (/10): greater than (>)",
          "id": 3035,
          "placeholder": "Enter Number"
        },
        {
          "answer": "{ '3037': { value: 120, t_id: [ 'C3' ] } }",
          "type": "number",
          "code": null,
          "question": "Systolic Blood Pressure (mmHg): greater than (>)",
          "id": 3037,
          "placeholder": "Enter Number"
        },
        {
          "answer": {
            "3040": {
              "value": 120,
              "t_id": [
                "C3"
              ]
            }
          },
          "type": "number",
          "code": null,
          "question": "Systolic Blood Pressure (mmHg): or less than (<)",
          "id": 3040,
          "placeholder": "Enter Number"
        },
        {
          "answer": "{ qn_id: 3042, value: 80, option_ids: [], t_id: [ 'C3' ] }",
          "type": "number",
          "code": null,
          "question": "Diastolic Blood Pressure (mmHg): greater than (>)",
          "id": 3042,
          "placeholder": "Enter Number"
        },
        {
          "answer": {
            "qn_id": 3045,
            "value": 80,
            "t_id": [
              "C3"
            ]
          },
          "type": "number",
          "code": null,
          "question": "Diastolic Blood Pressure (mmHg): or less than (<)",
          "id": 3045,
          "placeholder": "Enter Number"
        },
        {
          "answer":"{ '3047': { value: 90, option_ids: [], t_id: [ 'C5' ] } }",
          "type": "number",
          "code": null,
          "question": "Blood Sugar, Fasting (mg/dL): greater than (>)",
          "id": 3047,
          "placeholder": "Enter Number"
        },
        {
          "answer":"{ '3050': { value: 90, option_ids: [], t_id: [ 'C5' ] } }",
          "type": "number",
          "code": null,
          "question": "Blood Sugar, Fasting (mg/dL): or less than (<)",
          "id": 3050,
          "placeholder": "Enter Number"
        },
        {
          "type": "number",
          "code": null,
          "question": "Blood Sugar, Random (mg/dL): greater than (>)",
          "id": 3052,
          "placeholder": "Enter Number"
        },
        {
          "answer":"{ '3055': { value: 110, t_id: [ 'C5' ] } }",
          "type": "number",
          "code": null,
          "question": "Blood Sugar, Random (mg/dL): or less than (<)",
          "id": 3055,
          "placeholder": "Enter Number"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
]
